Last mission to win this war.
Operation Seawolf is a war, thriller, action film directed by Steven Luke.
During the last days of World War II, Germany, desperate for any last grasp to defeat
the allied powers, looked to their last remaining weapons and soldiers.
The German Navy and the last remaining U-Boats were formed together for one desperate last
mission – a mission to attack the United States Homeland, known as Operation Seawolf.
Captain Hans Kessler, a grizzled submarine commander from both World Wars, is called into
service to make one mission a success and help turn the tide of the war.
Hans Kessler, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Valentine, played by Aaron Courteau.
Commander Ingram, played by Frank Grillo.
Lt. Erich Reinhart, played by Andrew Stecker.
Sam L. Gravely Jr., played by Hiram A. Murray.
Lt. Randolf Lutz, played by Apostolos Gliarmis.
The Silent Service (Japanese: 沈黙の艦隊, Hepburn: Chinmoku no Kantai) is a
Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Kaiji Kawaguchi.
It was published in Kodansha's Weekly Morning manga magazine from
1988 to 1996 and collected in 32 tankōbon volumes.
The series was adapted into an anime television special and
original video animation (OVA) series by Sunrise.
The special was released in North America by Central Park Media.
A live-action film adaptation premiered in Japanese theaters in September 2023 and a sequel,
titled The Silent Service: The Battle of Arctic Ocean, premiered in September 2025.
In 1990, The Silent Service won the 14th Kodansha Manga
Award for the general manga category.
It has over 25 million copies in circulation, making it
one of the best-selling manga series.
The tone is intense.